export const ReactQuestion = [
    {
        question: "Who created React.js?",
        options: ["Jorden mike", "Jorden walke", "Time Lee", "Jorden Lee"],
        ans: 1
    }, 

    {
        question: "What is ReactJS?",
        options: ["user interface framework", "Sever-side Framework", "both a and b", "none of above"],
        ans: 0
    },

    {
        question: "Which of the following is the correct name of React.js?",
        options: ["React", "React.js", "ReactJS", "All of the above"],
        ans: 3
    },

    {
        question: "In which language is React.js written?",
        options: ["Python", "Java", "JAvascript", "PHP"],
        ans: 2
    },

    {
        question: "What is ReactJS mainly used for building?",
        options: ["Database", "Connectivity", "User interface", "Design platform"],
        ans: 2
    },

    {
        question: "How many elements can a valid react component return?",
        options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        ans: 0
    },

    {
        question: "What are arbitrary inputs of components in react also known as?",
        options: ["Elements", "Props", "Keys", "Ref"],
        ans: 1
    },

    {
        question: "Identify the smallest building block of React.JS.",
        options: ["Props", "Elements", "Components", "None of Above"],
        ans: 2
    },

    {
        question: "Which of the following function is used to change the state of react component?",
        options: ["this.setState()", "this.state()", "this.setChangeState()", "None of Above"],
        ans: 0
    },

    {
        question: "What is the use of the create-react-app command in the React.js application?",
        options: ["It is used to update a React app.", "It is used to create a new React app.", "It is used to install dependencies.", "None of the above."],
        ans: 1
    },
]